euroteam.net 2010-06-13

# Terms and Conditions

Free ticket hotline: 00800 EUROTEAM (00800 387 683 26). Available in Europe only. 

Please read this page carefully and in its entirety, it details important information on our policies and terms of service. Terms and Condition updated and valid from 21.4.2008.

**MAIN CONTENTS :**  
1\.   Status of Euroteam AS - Status of Purchaser.  
2\.   Contract Documents.  
3\.   Event Specific Terms and Conditions.  
4\.   Delivery of Tickets.  
5\.   Price and Payment.  
6\.   Warranty.  
7\.   Changes and Cancellation.  
8\.   Complaints.  
9\.   Force Majeure.  
10\. Purchaser’s Breach of Contract.  
11\. Indemnity.  
12\. Exclusive Remedies – Limitation of Liability..  
13\. Governing Law – Dispute Resolution..  
14\. Privacy Statement.

1\. Status of Euroteam AS - Status of Purchaser.

Euroteam AS (“Euroteam”) is an independent and privately owned company engaged in the business of buying and selling tickets and hospitality packages (the “Tickets”) for sports and cultural events and tournaments (the “Events”). Euroteam is in no way affiliated with any official organizer, venue or box office, unless otherwise specified. Any wish to purchase tickets, or similar, directly from the official organizer, venue or official box office, must be pursued directly towards such actors.

For Consumer purchases the these terms and conditions will only be valid till the extent that this is not in conflict with local consumer laws and regulations. For further details of laws and regulation in your Country we advise you to take contact with the local consumer protection agency in your area.

2\. Contract Documents.

This Contract and these Terms and Conditions shall apply to and govern all sale and purchase of Tickets deriving from [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/). Purchaser and Euroteam agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions accordingly. By clicking on the “Confirm” button, the agreement for sale and purchase of the Tickets (the “Contract”) is bindingly entered into on the Terms and Conditions as is set forth in the Contract.

The Contract consists of; (i) the Order Confirmation, (ii) the Order, (iii) any Event Specific Terms and Conditions, (iv) these General Terms and Conditions, and (v) any other information deriving from [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) applicable to the sale and purchase of Tickets. In the event of any conflict between the provisions of the references here above, they shall be given priority in the order as listed.

3\. Event Specific Terms and Conditions.

Euroteam reserves the right to revise the General Terms and Conditions at any time, and to add to the Contract a prevailing set of Event Specific Terms and Conditions valid and binding for a specific Event. Such amendments will be advised of by posts on[www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/), and may in particular be found at the bottom of [www.euroteam.net/Terms](http://www.euroteam.net/Terms). Purchaser is therefore advised to periodically check [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) for updates. Such revisions and amendments will be given retroactive effect as to apply to all relevant Contracts entered into. When ordering Tickets for the relevant Event, Purchaser hereby expressly agrees to be bound by such Event Specific Terms and Conditions posted on [www.euroteam.net/Terms](http://www.euroteam.net/Terms) prior to the date of the Event.

4\. Delivery of Tickets.

Euroteam shall be obliged to deliver the Tickets in accordance with the terms and conditions of the Contract. Euroteam will be responsible to send and/or deliver the Tickets to the address given by Purchaser. Purchaser is obliged to inform Euroteam of any change in address with respect to where the Tickets may be delivered. However, Euroteam may, at its complete discretion, instruct Purchaser to pick up the Tickets at a pick-up location specified by Euroteam in or nearby the city of the Event. In case of Purchaser’s pick-up of the Tickets, any relevant delivery charge paid by Purchaser will be refunded. Delivery shall take place upon arrival of the Tickets to the address appointed by Purchaser, or when made available on the relevant location for pick-up as the case may be, whichever occurs first. There after, the risk for the Tickets (including but not limited to the risk of loss of-, damage to- and theft of the Tickets) shall be transferred to Purchaser.

Euroteam may at its sole discretion request that Purchaser after ordering the Tickets, provides Euroteam with a copy of any credit cards used for ordering of Tickets or a copy of Purchasers identification papers, such as Purchaser’s passport. Euroteam is entitled to retain any ordered Tickets until such satisfactory documentation is received.

Purchaser shall warrant and ensure reception of the Tickets, and if necessary contact and actively liaise with the Postal/Courier Company, and/or any other delivery person, to make sure that the Tickets are received by Purchaser. Euroteam shall not be responsible for any delivery failures due to incomplete contact and delivery information given by Purchaser, neither lack of satisfactory reception facilities or cooperation as stated above.

Euroteam will in each Contract indicate date and time of delivery or pick-up of the Tickets. Such dates are for guidance only, and Euroteam reserves the right to deliver the Tickets on the actual day of the relevant Event, within a reasonable time prior to its start on the same day, without becoming in breach of the Contract. If the Tickets are not delivered within such a reasonable time on the same day, the provisions of Clause 6 shall apply.

Purchaser is hereby informed of that Euroteam may not be in possession of Tickets ordered hereunder at time of entry into Contract. Subsequent to formation of the Contract, Euroteam will subject to the other provisions of the Contract obtain such Tickets in the second hand market.

5\. Price and Payment.

Purchaser shall pay the Ticket price as stipulated in the Contract, and in accordance with the terms and conditions hereof. Invoices must be paid in its entirety within the due date(s) set forth in such invoice(s) or the Order Confirmation.

Pursuant to Norwegian law, Euroteam hereby discloses, and Purchaser hereby acknowledges, that the stated Ticket price in most cases contains a service charge or profit which has been added to the face value of, or to Euroteam`s price for, the Tickets. Typically, the price charged for a Ticket is substantially over face value. The amount charged over the face value of the Tickets represents Euroteam’s cost and mark up of obtaining the Tickets in the secondary market, and our fair compensation for the work and difficulty involved in obtaining Tickets for hard-to-get and sold-out Events.

Upon any breach of the provisions above in this Clause 5, Euroteam may, upon notice, terminate the Contract with immediate effect. Euroteam shall not incur any liability with respect to such termination, and reserves any right it may have at law or under contract for Purchasers’ default. Euroteam may in addition keep any partial payments made by Purchaser as compensation for costs incurred and/or loss of profit.

6\. Warranty.

In case of failure by Euroteam to deliver the full quantity of Tickets, if the Tickets are not delivered within a reasonable time on the day of the Event, or upon other breach of this warranty, Euroteam will, as the sole liability for breach of this warranty, refund to Purchaser any deposits and/or prepayments made by Purchaser and received by Euroteam for undelivered Tickets ordered under this Contract. In addition Euroteam shall pay as compensation a sum up to 200 % of any such deposits and/or prepayments made by Purchaser and received by Euroteam for undelivered Tickets hereunder. Such compensation shall not, however, exceed EUR 200 per Contract or Customer.

7\. Changes and Cancellation.

Upon its formation, the Contract shall be binding and Purchaser cannot cancel the Contract. Subject only to Clauses 6 and 7, all deposits and payments made are non refundable. However, should Purchaser want to cancel the Contract, Euroteam may, in its complete discretion, accept and may by refunding only 50 % of the deposit or prepayment made. Such cancellation must be requested in writing by Purchaser and confirmed in writing by Euroteam.

Double bookings may occur as a result of offline telephone booking and bookings during system maintenance. In case of such double bookings, Euroteam reserves the right to cancel the Contract for any reason within 48 hours after time of Purchaser’s submission of the Order. Without this affecting Euroteam’s cancellation right, notice of such cancellation due to double bookings will be sent to Purchaser by e-mail and/or by post within 48 hours thereafter if such addresses are made available to Euroteam. Any deposit paid and received will be refunded immediately, but Euroteam will not pay any extra compensation, and hereby waives any and all liability under contract or at law for such cancellations.

In case of cancellation of an entire Event, Euroteam reserves the right to cancel the Contract, and will, as the sole liability for such cancellation, refund relevant delivery charges paid and 90 % of the deposit or prepayment made and received. In case of deferment or cancellation of parts of an Event, Euroteam reserves the right to change or cancel the Contract accordingly, but waives any and all liability under contract or at law with respect to such change, deferment or part cancellation, and no refund or compensation will be made.

In case the start time of an Event is moved, and a new Event time is adjusted by less than 48 hours from the original Event time, the Contract shall remain valid and un-amended, and Purchaser shall pay the Contract price as stipulated in the Contract. If such start time of an Event is adjusted by more than 48 hours from the original Event time, Purchaser may without undue delay from he or she ought to gain knowledge of the adjustment claim a 90 % refund of the deposit or prepayment made and received. If no such claim is presented to Euroteam, the Contract shall remain binding and un-amended in accordance with the other provisions of the Contract for the new time set for the Event.

In case the Tickets purchased comprise extra services, such as hospitality package, hotel room, courier delivery, etc., Euroteam reserves the right to reasonably change the details of mentioned services in case any of the third party providers of such extra services change these services to Euroteam. Euroteam will warrant mentioned extra services towards Purchaser only to the extent that the third party providers effectively warrant the same towards Euroteam. Updated information regarding such extra services is available on[www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/). Upon change or cancellation of parts of such extra services, Purchaser shall not be entitled to cancel or change the Contract, but the Contract shall remain valid and binding on the terms set out herein. However, upon such change or cancellation, Purchaser may be entitled to claim a reduction in the Contract price if Euroteam does not provide equivalent replacement extra services. Such reduction in the Contract price shall correspond to the difference in value between the extra services initially purchased, and the ones actually delivered.

Euroteam operates with up to four different Ticket categories for an Event. The variations in the Ticket category are based on the categories of the Event organizer, the face value of the Tickets, and the seating locations. Euroteam’s categories are not always identical to the categories which the organizer of the Event operates with, and Purchaser hereby acknowledges and accepts that Euroteam may deliver Tickets which reasonably deviate from the Ticket category of the organizer of the Event without becoming in breach of the Contract. Subject to the above in this paragraph, in the case of delivery of Tickets in a lower Euroteam category than what originally ordered due to reasons within Euroteam’s control, Purchaser shall be entitled to a partial refund as calculated by Euroteam based on Euroteam’s Ticket category prices. For example: Euroteams current prices for an event are 300 EUR for cat.1 and 200 EUR for cat.2. You order one ticket cat.1 but you receive one cat. 2 ticket. In this case you are entitled to a 100 EUR refund from Euroteam.

Purchaser shall be obliged to give information about supporting preferences when ordering Tickets. Euroteam will endeavor to deliver Tickets with seating/located in accordance with the preferred and specified supporter section but may not warrant that these specifications are met. The parties therefore agree that Euroteam will not become in breach of the Contract due to not meeting such specifications. When Tickets are purchased for groups (2 or more persons), Euroteam only warrants seating/location pair wise for Euroteam Ticket category nos. 1 and 2. For Tickets ordered in Euroteam Ticket category nos. 3 and 4 however, these may be with restricted view and not adjacent.

Euroteam might not be able to inform about changes in the Event program or content. Purchaser is therefore requested to check the official Event organizer or Event website for any changes in the Event program or content.

8\. Complaints.

If the Purchaser has any complaints or desires to present a claim for refund regarding purchase of Tickets, such complaint or claim must be made in writing and received by Euroteam at the latest 9 weeks after the start date for the relevant Event. Complaints and claims must be sent in the format prescribed on [ www.Euroteam.net/EN/Complaints](http://www.euroteam.net/EN/Complaints). Purchaser hereby precludes any claim not properly received by Euroteam within this time limit and in the prescribed format. Euroteam will normally review a complaint or claim timely received within four (4) weeks after its receipt by Euroteam.

9\. Force Majeure.

Euroteam shall not be liable for any delay in the performance or non-performance of the Contract due an occurrence beyond its control, provided that such occurrence could not have been foreseen by Euroteam at the time of entry into the Contract and it could not have been avoided or its consequences overcome.

10\. Purchaser’s Breach of Contract.

If the Purchaser violates the terms of this Contract, Euroteam shall, as being the owner and operator of [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/), have the right to, at its option, bar Purchaser from any future use of [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/), terminate the Contract immediately and without notice, and/or take the appropriate legal action against Purchaser. Termination of the Contract due to the Purchaser’s breach of the Contract gives the Purchase no right to refunds of any payments made by Purchaser. Furthermore, Euroteam reserves any right and remedy it may have against Purchaser at law or under contract due to Purchaser’s default.

11\. Indemnity.

Subject to the provisions of Clauses 6 and 7, Purchaser shall release, defend, indemnify and hold harmless Euroteam, its subsidiaries, suppliers, affiliates, officers, agents and other partners and employees from:

  * Any loss, damage, liability, claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, incurred by Purchaser in relation to the Contract or use of[www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) (including also Purchaser’s use of [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) to provide a link to another website), such as, but not limited to Purchaser’s own special, consequential and indirect losses. 
  * Any loss, damage, liability, claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, incurred by third parties arising out of this Contract or Purchasers use of [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) (including also Purchaser’s use of [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) to provide a link to another website). 

12\. Exclusive Remedies – Limitation of Liability..

The liability for breach of the warranty as expressly stated in Clause 6, and for changes and cancellation as expressly stated in Clause 7, shall be Purchaser’s sole liability towards Euroteam for breach of the warranty, cancellation, changes or any default by Euroteam under this Contract.

Notwithstanding any other provision to the contrary herein, Euroteam`s maximum liability to Purchaser related to performance or non-performance of the Contract, including but not limited to the warranty liability hereunder, shall be limited to 200 % of the total value of deposit and prepayment made to – and received by Euroteam under the Contract.

13\. Governing Law – Dispute Resolution..

The relationship between Euroteam and Purchaser shall be governed and interpreted in accordance with Norwegian law, and the parties agree that the City Court of Oslo in Norway shall have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any dispute between the parties, which has not been resolved amicably within a reasonable time from the dispute arose. This shall apply without regard to any provisions, principles or rules deriving from private international law or from the Convention on the International Sale of Goods 1980.

14\. Privacy Statement.  
On [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/), Euroteam wishes to demonstrate its intention to respect and protect the privacy of Purchaser and other users. If Purchaser or other users have questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Euroteam AS  
Telephone: +47 2333 3500  
E-mail: On [contact@euroteam.net](mailto:contact@euroteam.net)  
Postal Address: Parkveien 25, 0350 Oslo, Norway

_14.1. Consent to store and handle personal information :_

Based on the clear information below, Purchaser hereby expressly and voluntarily agrees that Euroteam may store and use the information submitted by Purchaser (as requested on [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/)) for the purposes of executing the Contract, including but not limited to providing such information to third parties as deemed necessary for same purpose, and for the purposes as specified below in Clause 14.2.

_14.2. What information is sought when visiting the site and when registering? :_

When you register as a Purchaser or client with Euroteam, you will be asked a few personal questions, such as name, address, phone number and e-mail address. We will also ask you to choose a login name and a password. We need: 

Your address to be able to send you invoices, Order Confirmations and Tickets.  
Your e-mail address, to be able to send you Order Confirmations, newsletters and promotion material. If you do not wish to receive any newsletters and promotion material, you can cancel these mailings. Look below in item 14.3  
Your phone number in case we have to reach you quickly, e.g. if we are unable to deliver the ordered Tickets as indicated.  
To register domain names and IP addresses for use in internal statistics.  
To use "cookies" to monitor the parts of our web site that you prefer and the registration of languages.  
To register the promotion partner number of the promotion partner that directed you to the site, to be able to pay a promotion commission.  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate such information by making the change on our member information page, or by contacting Euroteam on the contact details as given above in this Clause 14..

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication, or by contacting Euroteam on the contact details as given above in this Clause 14.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

Euroteam is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers[www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/). Because Euroteam wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, Euroteam has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Euroteam on the contact details as given above in this Clause 14. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with Euroteam to resolve your concerns.

_14.3. Newsletters and received information :_

Anyone registered as a client on [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/), will be able to receive newsletters and information regarding Events, Tickets and hospitality packages. We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase Tickets and/or a hospitality package, but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us on the contact details as given above in this Clause 14. You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

_14.4. Sharing of information with others :_

Euroteam will only share information concerning you as a client with a third party, if a task has to be executed by this third party under the execution of the Contract. We will only give out information when it is absolutely necessary in order to execute such a task. It may also be of interest to make use of external consultants in connection with market surveys or similar to treat and maintain the customer relationship. All information shared with a third party is protected by confidentiality agreements. The information will not be used commercially nor used by the third party more than absolutely necessary in order to execute a task requested. Euroteam does not sell names, e-mail addresses or any other customer profile information to a third party.

_14.5. Cookies :_   
Euroteam strives to make use of the best technology and research at all times thus being able to offer our clients the most efficient, informative and interesting experiences. To achieve this, some of our business partners use "cookies". A "cookie" is a small text file, which our site sends to your "hard drive" when you have logged in on [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/). The next time you visit our site, the site will ask for the information registered in order to increase the efficiency of our content adapted to you. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

_14.6. Links :_   
[www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/)contains links to other web sites that are not owned or controlled by Euroteam. Please be aware that Euroteam is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web-site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected directly on [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/)..

_14.7. Safety :_   
[www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) has implemented a number of safety precautions to prevent loss and damage as a consequence of gathered or transferred information. We utilize Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology to secure the information registered by Euroteam. Credit card details will never be transmitted decrypted over the Internet or stored in any database at Euroteam. All stored information concerning our clients and Purchaser is protected behind a firewall. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link www.openssl.org.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our web-site, you may contact us on the contact details as given above in this Clause 14.

_14.8. Notification of Changes :_   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) and other places we deem appropriate, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will solicit for approval and post a notice on [www.euroteam.net](http://www.euroteam.net/) for 30 days.

_14.9. Legal Disclaimer :_

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.

In the case of conflict between the English Terms and Conditions and other linguistic versions, the English Terms and Conditions must prevail.
